atypon-link.com 2012-11-16

# Atypon | Privacy Policy

### What Information Do We Collect?

Atypon collects personal information in three ways—through information provided directly from our users and from information collected through web server logs.

### Information Supplied by Our Users

Atypon collects personal information, such as your email address, name, home or work address, and telephone number. Atypon does not collect any of this unique information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information to Atypon.

### Information from Web Server Logs

Atypon records and saves information about you from our web server logs such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the time and day you visited, and your browser type. This information is used to verify our records and to provide better service to you.

### Links to Other Sites

Atypon provides links to third party websites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to visit from Atypon so that you can understand how those websites collect, use, and share your information. Atypon is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Atypon site.

### Disclosure of your Personal Information to Third Parties

Atypon will not willfully disclose any individually identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission. Atypon may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or when, in the good faith belief that such action is necessary, to conform to the edicts of the law or to comply with legal process served on Atypon, to protect and defend the rights or property of Atypon, or to act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Atypon or members of the public.

### Protecting Your Information

While Atypon is committed to protecting your personal information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

We welcome your comments or questions.
